const FoodNutritionQuestions = [
    {
        question: "Which nutrient is the body's main source of energy?",
        options: ["Proteins", "Carbohydrates", "Vitamins"],
        correct_option: "Carbohydrates"
    },
    {
        question: "What nutrient is essential for building and repairing body tissues?",
        options: ["Proteins", "Fats", "Minerals"],
        correct_option: "Proteins"
    },
    {
        question: "Which vitamin is often referred to as the 'sunshine vitamin'?",
        options: ["Vitamin D", "Vitamin C", "Vitamin A"],
        correct_option: "Vitamin D"
    },
    {
        question: "What nutrient is important for healthy digestion and helps prevent constipation?",
        options: [ "Iron","Fiber", "Calcium",],
        correct_option: "Fiber"
    },
    {
        question: "Which mineral is essential for strong bones and teeth?",
        options: ["Calcium", "Potassium", "Magnesium"],
        correct_option: "Calcium"
    },
    {
        question: "What nutrient is the body's primary source of building blocks for cells and tissues?",
        options: ["Proteins", "Fats", "Carbohydrates"],
        correct_option: "Proteins"
    },
    {
        question: "Which food group provides the body with essential vitamins and minerals?",
        options: ["Dairy Products","Fruits and Vegetables",  "Meat and Poultry"],
        correct_option: "Fruits and Vegetables"
    },
    {
        question: "What nutrient is important for maintaining healthy skin and hair?",
        options: [ "Vitamin C", "Vitamin A","Vitamin E",],
        correct_option: "Vitamin A"
    },
    {
        question: "Which nutrient is essential for proper brain function and nerve transmission?",
        options: ["Omega-3 fatty acids", "Calcium", "Iron"],
        correct_option: "Omega-3 fatty acids"
    },
    {
        question: "What nutrient provides the highest amount of calories per gram?",
        options: ["Fats", "Proteins", "Carbohydrates"],
        correct_option: "Fats"
    }
];

export default FoodNutritionQuestions;
